Guide to the First Unitarian Congregational Society of Brooklyn records ARC.109
Brooklyn Historical Society
- Series 5: Unitarian Movement Files., 1850-1975; 1850-1945; 1 Linear Feet In 2 manuscript boxes.
  - AUA: Annual Meeting, 1917-1936, 1943 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - AUA: Board of Directors' Meetings, 1929, 1943 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - AUA: By-Laws and Organization, 1847, 1914-1932 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - AUA: Committee on New Americans, 1928-1930 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - AUA: Educational Institutions, 1850s, 1928-1932 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - AUA: Finance, Income and Expenditures, 1929-1934 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - AUA: Fund Raising: Contributions of First Unitarian Church, 1900-1943 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - AUA: Fund Raising: Maintenance Fund, 1930 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - AUA: General Conference, 1919, 1929, 1931 (Box 49, Folder 12-13)
  - AUA: International Congress, Foreign Relations Committee, 1922-1932 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - AUA: Layman's League, 1919-1922 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - AUA: Membership Drive, 1920-1922 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - AUA: Mid-Atlantic States Council: Metropolitan Conference, 1932-1940 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - AUA: Oxford Conference, 1936-1937 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - AUA: Publications Committee, 1930-1932 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - AUA: Social Relations Department, 1927-1933 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - AUA: Social Service Council, 1926 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - AUA: Wilbur, Earl, 1933 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Brooklyn: Charities and Welfare Associations, 1917-1940 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Brooklyn: Civic and Cultural Development, 1876-1945 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Flatbush Unitarian Church, 1932-1942, 1950, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Hollis Unitarian Church, 1934, 1937, 1942 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - New Jersey Unitarian Church Archives Survey, 1940 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Other Unitarian Churches, circa 1910s-1930s (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Salem Church, Massachusetts, 1917-1923 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Transylvanian Sister Church, 1920-1940 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Unitarian Conference of Mid-Atlantic States and Canada, 1911-1942 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Unitarian Foundation, 1926 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Unitarian Service Pension Society, 1916-1940 (Box 50, Folder 16)
- Series 6: Sunday School Books., 1842-1906; 1.25 Linear Feet In 3 manuscript boxes.
  The books are arranged alphabetically by subject.
  The Sunday School Books series contains small books and ledgers used by the Sunday School of the First Unitarian Church. Lists of names of teachers and students can be found in the Attendance Records Ledgers and the Directory and Secretary's Book. The books on the Annual Meetings of Teachers and the Sunday School Journal account the operations and concerns of the school. Sunday School classes were conducted by the Church of the Saviour at the Wall Street Ferry House on Furman Street until the building of Willow Place Chapel in 1876. Thus, it should be noted that the books in this series span the time before and after the building of the chapel and those interested in the Congregation's Sunday School should also check the Willow Place Chapel series. Some additional records on the Church's school can be found in the Subject Files series. Some financial records of the Sunday School can be found in the Financial Records series.
  - Annual Meetings of Teachers, 1887-1890 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Attendance Records Ledgers, 1842-1883 (Box 51, Folder 2-5)
  - Attendance Records Ledgers, 1889-1903 (Box 52, Folder 1-3)
  - Directory and Secretary's Book, 1877-1881 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Sunday School Journal, 1864-1880 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Superintendent's Record, 1901-1906 (Box 53, Folder 3)
- Series 7: Calendars., 1910-1952; 1.75 Linear Feet In 4 manuscript boxes.
  The calendars are arranged chronologically by year.
  The Calendars series contains the bound books that hold the orders of worship as well as flyers and pamphlets related to services. Programs to special services and events are often included as well. Some of the calendars were in the possession of Minister John H. Lathrop and include some of his annotations and notes. For additional orders see the files on "Sermons and Orders of Worship" within the John H. Lathrop Files
  - Calendars, 1910-1923 (Box 54, Item 1-13)
  - Calendars, 1923-1935 (Box 55, Item 1-12)
  - Calendars, 1935-1946 (Box 56, Item 1-11)
  - Calendars, 1946-1952 (Box 57, Item 1-6)
- Series 8: Registers., 1841-1930; 1.25 Linear Feet In 3 manuscript boxes.
  Registers are arranged alphabetically by description.
  The registers in this series track the christenings, marriages, and funerals carried out by the Congregation. Willow Place Chapel had its own functions separate from the Church of the Saviour and kept its own registers which can also be found in this series. The Willow Place Chapel registers also contain substantive commentary on the families making up that portion of the Congregation, including notes on employment, illness, marital problems, and other issues. Some registers also contain additional information on the Sunday School and charity loans. For additional records of christenings, marriages, deaths, and member rolls of the Church, one should check the reports of the Ministers to the Trustees in Trustee Records, the "History" folders within the Subject Files, and lists of parishioners kept by John H. Lathrop in the John H. Lathrop Files.
  - General Register, 1893-1912 (Box 57, Item 7)
  - Marriage and Christening Register, 1841-1890 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Marriage and Christening Register, 1895-1900 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Willow Place Chapel Registers, 1889-1904 (Box 58, Folder 3-5)
  - Willow Place Chapel Registers, 1904-1912 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Willow Place Chapel Register of Members, 1921-1930 (Box 59, Folder 2)
- Series 9: Buildings and Construction., 1833-1956; 1.25 Linear Feet In 3 manuscript boxes.
  Materials in Buildings and Construction are arranged alphabetically by description.
  The Buildings and Construction series pertains to buildings constructed, purchased, and maintained by the First Congregation. Among these buildings is the Gothic Revival style Church of the Saviour of the Brooklyn Heights neighborhood, built in 1844. The series includes the original plans and specifications submitted by its architect, Minard Lafever. In addition to plans, specifications, and alterations made on the buildings, the series contains financial information related to the properties and documents on embellishments to the buildings such as the Church's stained glass windows and marble baptismal font. There is also information on the pews of the Church of the Saviour and some of its renters. In addition to the Church of the Saviour other buildings in this series include the Parish House (50 Monroe Place), the Parsonage (98 Pierrepont St), the Pierrepont Chapel (adjacent to the Church of the Saviour), and 123 Pierrepont Street. Documents related to Willow Place Chapel and Columbia House are collected in the Willow Place Chapel and Columbia House series. For information on the organ of the Church of the Saviour refer to the Subject Files series.
  - 123 Pierrepont Street, 1938-1944 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    Moved to oversize box 3:
    Seven blueprints of 123 Pierrepont Street.
  - Church of the Saviour: Alterations and Repairs, 1904-1941 (Box 60, Folder 2-4)
    One oversize plan with diagrams of alterations, Undated (from Folder 2)
  - Church of the Saviour: Baptismal Font, 1847 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Church of the Saviour: Pews, 1833-1930s (Box 60, Folder 6-7)
    - One floor plan of pews with pew numbers and names of subscribers, 1844 (from Folder 6)
    - One floor plan of pews with pew numbers, Undated (from Folder 7)
  - Church of the Saviour: Plans and Specifications, 1842 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Church of the Saviour: Undercroft Alterations, 1923, 1938 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    One sketch of alteration plans, Undated.
  - Heating, 1937-1940 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Inspection Certificates, 1900-1949 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Insurance, 1881-1939 (Box 61, Folder 3-4)
  - Inventory, 1942 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Parish House: Alterations and Repairs, 1911-1937 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Parish House: Construction Bills, 1937-1938 (Box 61, Folder 7-9)
  - Parish House: Construction purchase orders, 1937 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Parish House: Contract Work, 1937 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Parsonage (98 Pierrepont Street), 1890-1953 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Three blueprints of stairway, doorway, and front of building, c.1930's-1940's
    - One sketch paper plan of first floor and basement, c. 1930's-1940's
  - Parsonage: Sale of, 1952 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Pierrepont Chapel, 1867-1869 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Pierrepont Chapel: Additions, 1905-1906 (Box OS-4)
  - Pierrepont Chapel: Construction and Renovations, 1913-1921 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Property Restrictions, 1910-1942 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Screens in Memory of Alfred, Annie, and Katherine White, circa 1922 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    Four blueprints of arch and screens, c.1922
  - Taxes and Assessments, 1907-1940 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Windows: Beatitudes Window, 1944-1947 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Windows: Clerestory Windows, 1912, 1930-1956 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Windows: Forbes Window, 1913 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Windows: Rose Window, 1913 (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Moved to Oversize Box 3: One blueprint of window fixture and design moved to oversize box
  - Windows: Tiffany Windows, 1905-1949 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Oversize Flat Box 3 (Box OS 3, Folder -)
- Series 10: Willow Place Chapel and Columbia House, 1865-1972; 5 Linear Feet In 12 manuscript boxes.
  Materials in the Willow Place Chapel and Columbia House" series are arranged alphabetically by description.
  Willow Place Chapel was built in 1876 under the direction of Alfred T. White who was seeking a more proper setting for the settlement school under his charge. The Chapel functioned somewhat separately from the Church of the Saviour and conducted its own evening services as well as adopting the First Congregation's Sunday School. In addition to these tasks, some other classes (such as in music or sewing), clubs, and welfare work operated out of Willow Place Chapel. In 1906 Columbia House was added to the settlement complex and carried on its own outreach and community work in conjunction with Willow Place Chapel. The Willow Place Chapel and Columbia House series contains the records related to the work carried on within these buildings and on behalf of the members including annual and trustee reports, deacon meeting minutes, Sunday school records, and the records of the Chapel Association. The series also holds relevant building records in regards to construction and alterations, financial information including accounts and salaries, various records on clubs and events that functioned out of the Chapel, and records related to health and social work carried out by the Chapel's staff. Prior to the establishment of Willow Place Chapel these tasks, particularly social and settlement work, were done at the Furman Street Mission. Reports and other records relevant to work done at the Furman Street Mission can be found in this series, particularly among material before 1876.
  For more on the Congregation's Sunday school, see the series Sunday School Books. For registers pertaining to services and members of the Willow Place Chapel, see the Registers series. Some financial records of the Sunday School can be found in the Financial Records series.
  - 50th Anniversary, 1915 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - 97th Company, 1890-1892 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Accounts Ledger, 1906-1920 (Box 63, Folder 3-4)
  - Alfred T. White Community Center, 1962 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - American Unitarian Association, 1917-1919 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Annual Meeting Reports, 1922-1939 (Box 63, Folder 7-8)
  - Annual Meeting Reports, 1940-1946 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Annual Picnic, 1915-1922 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - "B" Miscellaneous, circa 1910s (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Bequests: Windows, Lanterns and Banners, 1892-1932 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Better Times, the Weekly Welfare Magazine, 1926 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Board of Education, 1922-1947 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Boy Scouts, 1917-1918 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Boys' Clubs, 1915-1916 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Brooklyn Bureau of Charities, 1916-1919 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Brooklyn Trust Company, 1880s, 1920s (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Budgets, 1914-1922 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Buildings: Alterations and Repairs, 1906-1924 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Buildings: Contracts, 1905, 1925 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Buildings: Heating, 1924-1925 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Buildings: Insurance, 1925-1937 (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Buildings: Specifications, 1875 (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Buildings: Specifications, 1905 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Burke Relief Foundation, 1916-1917 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - "C" Miscellaneous, 1916-1917 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Calendars, 1921-1924 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Calendar Notices, 1918-1919 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Camps, 1917-1918 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Cash Accounts System, circa 1910s (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Cash Books, Receipts and Disbursements, 1909-1925 (Box 65, Folder 8-9)
    One ledger of Receipts and Disbursements, 1920-1925.
  - Chapel Association: Annual Meetings and By-Laws, 1890-1911 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Chapel Association: Meeting Minutes, 1914-1917 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Chapel Association: Meeting Minutes Book, 1912-1925 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Chapel House News, 1912, 1913 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Children's Aid Society: Summer Vacation, 1920 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Children's Year, 1918-1919 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Christmas Services, 1908-1920 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Citizenship and Americanization, circa 1918 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Clubs and Entertainments, 1913-1922 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Clubs: By-Laws, circa 1910s (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Clubs: Suggestions, circa 1910s (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Columbia Civic Club, 1917 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Columbia House, 1918-1944 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Columbia House: Accounts Ledger, 1919-1920 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Columbia House: Brass Band, 1917-1918 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Columbia House: Music School, 1919-1936 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Columbia House: Reports to the Treasurer, 1921-1922 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Columbia House: Sewing School and Library, 1928-1946 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Columbia House: Summer Vacation Work, 1915-1941 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Columbia Men's Club, 1916-1917 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Community Councils, 1919-1920 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Constitution and By-Laws, circa 1910s (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Country Fortnight Outings, 1918 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - "D" Miscellaneous, circa 1916 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Deacons: Meeting Minutes, 1943-1951 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - "E" Miscellaneous, 1917 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Easter Services, 1904-1916 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Edison Electric Illuminating Co., 1916-1917 (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Educational Dramatic League, circa 1910s (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - Employment Agencies and Bureaus, circa 1910s (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - "F" Miscellaneous, 1915-1921 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Finances, 1916-1948 (Box 68, Folder 2-7)
  - Finances: Accounts and Statements, 1917-1923 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Finances: Analysis, 1921 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Finances: Salary and Other Disbursements, 1917-1918 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Food Selection and Preparation, 1917 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Form Letters, 1919-1921 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Fourth of July Committee, 1916-1919 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Fundraising, 1907 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Furman Street Mission, 1867-1869 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - "G" Miscellaneous, 1917 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - "H" Miscellaneous, 1916-1918 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Health Clinics, 1916-1920 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - History, 1865-1914, 1972 (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Infantile Paralysis, 1916-1917 (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - Intersettlement Athletic League, 1916 (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - "L" Miscellaneous, 1917, 1920 (Box 69, Folder 15)
  - Lantern Slides, circa 1910s (Box 69, Folder 16)
  - Lathrop, John H., 1918-1924 (Box 69, Folder 17)
  - "M" Miscellaneous, 1916-1920 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Merger with Pierrepont Chapel, 1926 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Military Census, circa 1917 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Ministers, 1886, 1915-1930 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Monday Club, 1908-1914 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Mothers' Aid Day Nursery, 1911 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - "N" Miscellaneous, 1918-1924 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - "P" Miscellaneous, 1919 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Plays, circa 1910s (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Programs, 1890, 1912-1922 (Box 70, Folder 10-11)
  - Refurbishing (Baker Drawings), circa 1915 (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - One sketch of alterations and design for message board, Undated.
    - One sketch of turned wood candlestick, Undated.
  - Reports, 1868-1927 (Box 70, Folder 13-14)
  - Reports to the Trustees, 1867-1907 (Box 71, Folder 1-6)
  - Reports to the Trustees, 1908-1926 (Box 72, Folder 1-4)
  - Resolution: Unity with First Congregation, 1951 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Riverside Improvement Association: Zoning Restrictions, 1906-1925 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    Two blueprints of proposed cable and box for NY & NJ Telephone Company
  - Settlements, 1915-1923 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Special Services, 1871-1923 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Staff: Paid and Voluntary, 1908-1928 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Summer Work, 1920-1921 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Sunday School: Curriculum, 1920s-1940s (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Sunday School: List of Early Teachers, 1916-1926 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Sunday School: Outline of Mission, Undated (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Sunday School: Questionnaires, 1920s (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Sunday School: Reports, 1905-1923 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Sunday School: Teachers and Pupils Book, 1865-1917 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Titles, Deeds, and Leases, 1875-1947 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Two deeds of indenture between the Board of Education and Trustees of the Church, 1875
    - Two maps/plans of the area bordered by Columbia Place, State Street, Willow Place, and Joralemon Street, 1875 and 1947
  - Treasurer, 1918-1920 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Treasurer: Accounts Record Book, 1931-1941 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - War Correspondence, 1918 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - War Savings Committee, 1918 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    Moved to oversize:
    Three War Savings Stamps propaganda posters, c. 1918
  - Willow Place Chapel News, 1921-1927 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Women's Club, 1930s-1940s (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Wonderland, 1921-1922 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - YMCA, 1920 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Oversize Flat Box 1 (Box OS 1, Folder -)
  - Oversize Flat Box 2 (Box OS 2, Folder -)
  - Oversize Flat Box 3 (Box OS 3, Folder -)
- Series 11: Financial Records., 1833-1956; 8 Linear Feet In 12 manuscript boxes and 5 oversize flat boxes.
  Files and items are arranged alphabetically by description.
  The Financial Records series holds many of the Church's records regarding collecting and disbursing funds for its operations as well as for Willow Place Chapel, the Sunday School, Missionary Fund, and other programs. General financial statements of the Congregation are within this series. The series includes records of disbursements from the Charity Fund, Friendship Fund, and Minister's Discretionary Fund (the Charity Fund was used to make payments to congregants in need until 1923 when it was replaced by the Friendship Fund. The Friendship Fund was closed in 1940 and its purpose subsumed into the Minister's Discretionary Fund, which was also used for such payments prior to 1940.) In addition to the records of the Treasurer, budgets, investments, and fund raising, this series also contains ledgers on subscriber dues and pew rentals, including a book of the original deeds to the pews. Records on the receipts of the Church and ledgers of Offerings to the Church are another source of lists of pews renters and subscribers. The Church's investments include mortgages, so there is some information on individual residential mortgages including amounts, debtors, and properties.
  The Housekeeping Scribe's Chronicle is a record of expenses for club meetings and events and thus doubles as a resource of menus and club member rolls.
  - Appraisal of Property and Furnishings, 1932, 1939 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Budgets, 1916-1954 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Budgets: Correspondence, 1924-1935 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Budgets: Correspondence, 1936-1942 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Charity Fund: Minutes and Account Book, 1871-1902 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Charity Fund / Friendship Fund: Account Book, 1902-1940 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Charity Fund: Check Books, 1902-1923 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Charity Fund / Friendship Fund: Notes and Correspondence, 1918-1940 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Charity Fund: Vouchers (Brackett, Treasurer), 1899-1911 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Charity Fund: Vouchers (White, Treasurer), 1911-1921 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Charity Fund / Friendship Fund: Vouchers (Frothingham, Treasurer), 1921-1940 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Collection Plate, Church and Chapel, 1940-1947 (Box 76, Folder 4-6)
  - Endowment Investments, 1911-1941 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Endowment Investments: Mortgages, 1890s-1940s (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Fund Raising: Charity and Missionary Committee, 1897-1919 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Fund Raising: Easter Offertory, 1935 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Fund Raising: Every Member Visitation, 1934, 1939 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Fund Raising: Loyalty Week, 1934-1935 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Fund Raising: Methods, 1931, 1939 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Fund Raising: Pledge Cards, 1918-1919 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Fund Raising: Special Appeals, 1919 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Fund Raising: Survey Committee: Questionaire and Replies, 1938 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Fund Raising: Survey Committee: Survey and Recommendations, 1938 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - General Finances Journal, 1921-1935 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - General Finances Ledger, 1908-1935 (Box 78, Folder 1-2)
  - Housekeeping Scribe's Chronicle, 1930s (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Housekeeping Scribe's Chronicle Book, 1927-1945 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Income for Special Funds, 1921-1935 (Box 79A, Folder 1)
  - Investments, 1895-1928 (Box 79A, Folder 2-4)
  - Missionary Fund: Collections Ledger, 1898-1910 (Box 79A, Folder 5)
  - Minister's Discretionary Fund: Check Books, 1932-1935 (Box 79B, Folder 1)
  - Minister's Discretionary Fund: Check Books, 1935-1941 (Box 79B, Folder 2)
  - Minister's Discretionary Fund: Check Books, 1941-1945 (Box 79B, Folder 3)
  - Minister's Discretionary Fund: Check Book and Correspondence, 1945-1949 (Box 79B, Folder 4)
  - Minister's Discretionary Fund: Check Books, 1946, 1949-1952 (Box 79B, Folder 5)
  - Minister's Discretionary Fund: Correspondence and Notes, 1930-1951 (Box 79B, Folder 6)
  - Offerings Ledgers, 1929-1936 (Box 80, Item 1-4)
  - Pews: Original Deeds and Transfers, 1844-1901 (Box 81, Item 1)
  - Pews: Rental Ledgers, 1840-1886 (Box 81, Item 2-5)
  - Pews: Rental Ledgers, 1886-1921 (Box 82, Item 1-4)
  - Pledges Ledger, 1922 (Box 83, Item 1)
  - Receipts and Distribution Ledger, 1911-1921 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Receipts and Expenditures Ledger, 1914-1921 (Box 84, Folder 2-4)
  - Receipts and Expenditures Ledger, 1921-1927 (Box 85, Folder 1-4)
  - Receipts and Expenditures Ledger, 1929-1935 (Box 86, Item 1)
  - Receipts and Expenditures: Balance Sheets, 1923-1932 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Receipts and Expenditures: Overview, 1893-1913 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Reports, 1921-1944 (Box 87, Folder 3-7)
  - Reports, 1945-1956 (Box 88, Folder 1-2)
  - Subscribers Dues Book, 1842-1844 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Sunday School Accounts Ledger, 1866-1908 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Treasurer: Bank Account Book, 1845-1846 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Treasurer: Correspondence, 1910s-1940s (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Treasurer's General Ledger and Cash Book, 1833-1840 (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Treasurer's General Ledger and Cash Book, 1842-1859, 1866-1884 (Box 89, Folder 1-2)
  - Treasurer's General Ledger and Cash Book, 1884-1912 (Box 90, Folder 1-2)